Skillberry Store. A smart skills repository for agentic
workflows.
Install with pip, start with make docker-run. Web UI on
port 8002, REST API on 8000. Live in under a minute.
Import any Anthropic skill via GitHub URL, zip file, or
local folder. One call — 66 tools and 43 snippets imported
instantly.
The Skills library auto-tags every skill with quality,
performance, and security scores generated by the AI
plugins on import.
Execute any tool with a JSON body — via the UI dialog or
the sbs CLI. Every execution runs in a Docker sandbox,
fully isolated.
The Content Evaluator and Security Scanner automatically
score skills on import. The Summarizer scored 9 for
quality, 8 for performance, 8 for security.
Three more plugins: Deduplicator finds near-identical
skills, Creator generates code from text, Optimizer runs
Claude Code to improve skills.
Virtual MCP Servers give each skill its own MCP endpoint.
Virtual NFS mounts skills as filesystems. Prometheus and
Jaeger built in.
That's Skillberry Store — one service for every skill your
agents need. Find us at github.com slash skillberry-ai
slash skillberry-store.