Welcome to Skillberry Store — a smart skills repository
for agentic workflows.
Skillberry Store centralises every tool your AI agents
need. Upload once, execute anywhere. It manages tools,
skills, and snippets with semantic search, lifecycle
management, virtual MCP servers, and a plugin ecosystem.
Installation is simple. Install with pip, optionally
bundle the AI plugins. Run with Docker using a single make
command. The web UI starts on port 8002, the REST API on
8000, and the MCP control endpoint is ready for any AI
client.
The auto-generated CLI is called sbs. Built on restish, it
mirrors every REST endpoint. Run sbs connect to point it
at your server. Skills, tools, snippets, virtual servers,
and admin commands are all available.
Let's import a skill. Three paths are supported: GitHub
URL, zip file, or local folder. Here we point the API at
the PPTX skill on disk. The response confirms 66 tools and
43 snippets created in one call.
The web UI starts automatically. From the dashboard
navigate to Skills, Tools, Snippets, virtual servers,
Plugins, Observability, and Admin.
The Skills library shows our two imported skills — pptx
with 66 tools, summarizer with 29. Tags like
quality-score, performance-score, and security-score were
auto-applied by the AI plugins on import.
The Import Anthropic Skill dialog offers three sources:
GitHub URL, zip file for air-gapped environments, or local
folder for CI/CD pipelines. One click imports the full
skill tree — tools, snippets, and documentation.
Here's the pptx skill after import — 66 tools, 43
snippets, full metadata. You can export back to Anthropic
format, edit metadata, or delete with a cascade option to
clean up all linked objects.
The Summarizer skill: 29 tools, 2 snippets. The evaluator
scored it 9 out of 10 for quality, 8 for performance, 8
for security. Scores are searchable and filterable across
the library.
The Tools page shows all 95 tools in one sortable table.
Filter by tags, switch between text and semantic search,
and select multiple tools for bulk export or deletion.
Clicking a tool opens its detail page — programming
language, packaging format, dependencies, and the JSON
parameter schema. A Source Code tab shows the raw Python
module.
Hit Execute to run a tool. Parameters go in as JSON, and
the tool runs inside a Docker sandbox — isolated from the
host. From the CLI: sbs execute-tool with a body flag.
Same sandbox, scriptable.
Snippets are code fragments and docs imported with the
skill. Syntax-highlighted and searchable — perfect for
shared utility code.
Virtual MCP Servers expose a skill's tools as a standalone
MCP endpoint. Each gets its own port and SSE URL — connect
Claude, Cursor, or any MCP client directly.
Virtual NFS Servers expose a skill as a mountable
read-only filesystem over WebDAV or NFSv3 — Claude Code
and rclone can read files without the REST API.
The Plugins page shows all AI-powered extensions. Enable
or disable each independently. Let's walk through the five
key plugins.
The Content Evaluator tags skills and tools with quality,
performance, and security scores. The Summarizer scored 9
for quality, 8 for performance, 8 for security. Each score
includes a written explanation. Triggered on import or on
demand.
The Security Evaluator finds vulnerabilities — path
traversal, injection, missing auth. The pptx skill scored
4 out of 10 because it accepts arbitrary file paths with
no validation. Visible as a security-score tag before you
deploy.
The Skill Deduplicator uses LLM semantic comparison to
find near-identical skills. When duplicates are found, a
notification appears with Keep or Delete decisions. The
decision API lets you automate this in CI pipelines.
The Snippet Creator generates code from a natural language
description. Describe what you want, the LLM writes it,
infers the language and tags, and saves it to the store.
No copy-paste. Works with OpenAI, WatsonX, or LiteLLM.
The Skill Optimizer exports a skill, runs Claude Code in a
RunSpace container, and imports the optimized result with
an optimized suffix. Rationale and changes are saved as
metadata. Safe to re-run any time.
From the CLI, use sbs search-tools to find the right tool,
then sbs execute-tool with a JSON body. Results pipe into
jq, files, or any CI pipeline. Every operation is
scriptable.
Built-in observability: live time-series charts for
skills, tools, snippets, and system metrics. Prometheus on
port 8090. Jaeger traces. Drop a Grafana dashboard on top
for full monitoring.
The architecture is layered: Web UI and REST API at the
top, MCP frontend and virtual NFS alongside, core data
model in the middle, Docker sandbox and pluggable storage
below, and the AI plugin layer at the base.
That's Skillberry Store — one service for every skill your
agents need. Install with pip, start with make docker-run,
live in under a minute. Find us at github.com slash
skillberry-ai slash skillberry-store.